azendoo.com 2017-05-19

# Azendoo - Easy project management & team collaboration

## Privacy

Azendoo is founded on the principles of sharing tasks or files and collaborating as teams. We know that you care about how your personal information is used and shared; reason why security of data and privacy are a priority for us.

This Privacy Statement describes Azendoo's treatment of personal information that Azendoo gathers when you are on our websites and when you use our services. By visiting the Azendoo website and by subscribing to our service, you are accepting the practices outlined in this document. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Azendoo does not own or control, or to individuals that Azendoo does not employ or manage.

### Information collected

You can visit Azendoo website without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. 

However, in case of request for information or registration to Azendoo services, we may ask you to provide basic contact information and details about your company / your professional interests as well as information about the expected use of our services. 

We collect and store  personal information  such as your name or email, which are retained only if deliberately submit them: 

  * via a registration forms, a survey and other online forms; 
  * in order to get support; 
  * when your request a call back or information about our products. 

When purchasing the services, we require you to provide us with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the services.

### Basically,

We mainly collect information to make Azendoo services accessible and useful for you.

### Use of information

We use the information collected on our websites through contact forms to provide you with the services that you request. 

We may occasionally use the information collected to provide you with additional information on services, partners, promotions and Azendoo events. 

All data collected strictly remain for Azendoo SAS internal use only. Azendoo SAS is the sole owner of the information collected on its websites. 

We may use your personal information to: 
  * prevent and detect fraud or any other prohibited or illegal activities; 
  * protect the security and integrity of Azendoo websites and services; 
  * fulfill your requests for registration; 
  * process your online services orders; 
  * facilitate the use of Azendoo websites and services; 
  * help us customize content and make it closer to your needs; 
  * inform you of any important news on Azendoo, relevant to you; 
  * inform you of new services release and product updates; 
  * communicate with you about technical or functional problems; 
  * send you special offers and events that may interest you; 
  * promote our products and services on our website and those of our partners. 

We may also use the information collected to improve Azendoo websites and services.

### Basically,

Collected information also enable you to help us improve our services and stay in contact with us

### Sharing your Information

We promise not to share or sell, rent or trade your personal and confidential information with any third party for commercial purposes. We will share your personal information only with other Azendoo entities and / or partners exclusively for above described purposes. 

Azendoo SAS uses third-party applications, web services and external hosting services to provide the hardware, network, storage, and all other technology required to allow exceptional quality access to Azendoo websites and services. Whenever possible, we strive to ensure that our partners are aligned with our privacy policy.

### Basically,

Your information is safe with us. Other than publicly available, we do not share it with anyone. We do not sell your information.

### Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your web browser. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the choice to accept it or not. Some of our business partners, like advertisers, may use cookies on our website. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies. 

For some of its services and websites, Azendoo uses cookies or other technologies in order to offer you the best possible service and user experience, as well as easier navigation during your next visit: 
  * identify you as a user account holder;
  * ask you to re-enter your password after a certain period without activity to protect you against unsolicited access;
  * remember your preferences and settings;
  * estimate our audience and total traffic;
  * improve our services and websites.

### Basically,

To remember you, Azendoo services and web site use cookies. It's safe.

### Improvements of our web sites and services

Azendoo uses Google Analytics and other traffic analysis technologies in order to understand and optimize your use of our websites and services. Through cookies we can collect specific data (viewed pages, downloads, clicked links, connection time, IP address, domain name, parameters or system configurations, etc.). 

You can disable Google Analytics analysis of your specific navigation data through an additional module of your browser at the following address: [ tools.google.com ](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Basically

We track and analyse trafic to improve our web sites and to make our services better.

### Limitation of responsibility

Links to other websites are available from Azendoo websites and services. If you click on these links, you leave our websites and services. Azendoo SAS is in no way responsible for the content and / or privacy policy of those other websites. Azendoo does not warrant or approve the contents or resources that such sites provide access to, and excludes all liability and warranty with respect to such content. If you decide to access such sites, you do so at your own risk.

### Basically,

Azendoo SAS shall be responsible only for its own web sites and services.

### Contact Us

YOU EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE AUTHORITY TO ACCEPT THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THAT YOU HAVE READ THIS DOCUMENT AND UNDERSTAND THE RIGHTS, OBLIGATIONS, TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREIN. BY CLICKING ON THE ACCEPT BUTTON AND/OR CONTINUING TO USE AZENDOO SERVICES, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS HEREIN. 

You have the ability to review, change and correct the personally identifiable information you provide us. As a registered user, you can access, correct or update your account or other personal information. You may also request that we remove from our databases the information you provided when you registered with Azendoo by contacting us at support@azendoo.com. 

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the information practices of Azendoo website and services should be directed to Azendoo SAS by email at [ legal@azendoo.com ](mailto:legal@azendoo.com) or by mailing: 

Azendoo SAS, Legal Service   
87 Quai des Queyries,   
33100 Bordeaux, France

### Basically,

Any question? write us or send en email to legal@azendoo.com

Last updated on February 1, 2012
